<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="wi_lib_name" translatable="false">WorkInspector</string>
    <string name="wi_no_workers_found">No workers found</string>
    <string name="wi_error_generic">An error has occurred</string>
    <string name="wi_state_queued">Queued</string>
    <string name="wi_state_running">Running</string>
    <string name="wi_state_succeeded">Succeeded</string>
    <string name="wi_state_failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="wi_state_blocked">Blocked</string>
    <string name="wi_state_cancelled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="wi_state_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="wi_attempt_count">Attempt count: %d</string>
    <string name="wi_input_data">Input data</string>
    <string name="wi_output_data">Output data</string>
    <string name="wi_enqueued_at">Enqueued at</string>
    <string name="wi_repeat_interval">Repeat interval</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_unknown">Stop reason that is used in cases when worker did stop, but the reason for this is unknown. For example, when the app abruptly stopped due to a crash or when a device suddenly ran out of the battery</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_cancelled_by_app">The worker was cancelled directly by the app, either by calling cancel methods or enqueueing uniquely named worker with a policy that cancels an existing worker</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_preempt">The job was stopped to run a higher priority job of the app</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_timeout">The worker used up its maximum execution time and timed out</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_device_state">The device state (eg. Doze, battery saver, memory usage, etc) requires WorkManager to stop this worker</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_constraint_battery_not_low">The requested battery-not-low constraint is no longer satisfied</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_constraint_charging">The requested charging constraint is no longer satisfied</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_constraint_connectivity">The requested connectivity constraint is no longer satisfied</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_constraint_device_idle">The requested idle constraint is no longer satisfied</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_constraint_storage_not_low">The requested storage-not-low constraint is no longer satisfied</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_quota">The app has consumed all of its current quota</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_background_restriction">The app is restricted from running in the background</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_app_standby">The current standby bucket requires that the job stop now</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_user">The user stopped the job. This can happen either through force-stop, adb shell commands, uninstalling, or some other UI</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_system_processing">The system is doing some processing that requires stopping this job</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason_estimated_app_launch_time_changed">The system\'s estimate of when the app will be launched changed significantly enough to decide this worker shouldn\'t be running right now</string>
    <string name="wi_stop_reason">Stop reason</string>
    <string name="wi_period_count">Runs count: %d</string>
</resources>